CURRICULUM VITAE

MUSA-AZEEZ, Taslim Eniola

A. PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a friendly and proficient full stack web developer with zeal for developing problem solving-system with several year of experience in learning modern web developement skill and developement stacks. I am an excellent team player with great interpersonal skill including several collaborations with other developer both far and near. I have developed a number of web sites and web applications that render a service or solves a problem.

Notable among these projects is TranXfer Cloud: A online based file storage where users can store files and retrieve them on a laterdate. Another notable project is an Online Medical Diagnostics System: An online portal where patients can interact with a bot which queries them for symptoms and can predict with a high level of accuracy whether the patient is infected with Covid 19 or not. These projects earned me my expertice and proficiency which gives me an edge over a large number of developers out there.

B. PERSONAL DATA

Name Musa-Azeez, Taslim Eniola

Date of Birth 19th of April, 2001

Nationality Nigerian

State of Origin Oyo

Permanent Home Address Block B, Plot 11, Pheonix Gasline, Ogijo, Ogun State.

Present Position Undergraduate

Contact Details Email <u>taslim.eniolla@gmail.com</u>

Phone <u>0708-471-2978</u>



C. EDUCATION

2017 Till Date

B.Sc. in Information & Communication Science (Faculty of Communication & Information Sciences), University

of Ilorin, Nigeria. P.O.Box 1515. Maintained a Second Class Upper GPA Till Date.

2016 General Certificate Examination, Government Girls Secondary School, FESTAC, Lagos State, Nigeria. (2

Distinctions, 6 Credits, 1 pass).

2014 - 2016 Senior Secondary School, Great Esteem Secondary School, Sanya Junction, Apapa-Oshodi Express Way, Lagos.

2011 - 2014 Junior Secondary School, Iman College, Mopol Junction, Off Ago-Okota Road, Amuwo-Odofin, Mile 2, Lagos.

2006 - 2011 Primary Leaving Certificate, Amuwo-Odofin Muslim Community Private School (AOMCPS). Maintained Top 3

Position from Primary One to Five

D. INTERNSHIP

Mar. - Sept., 2020 SOFTRAYS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

I had my internship program at the above mentioned organization where I got to acquire some skills and got certifications for them. The skill I acquired are listed below:

Graphics Design

• Full Stack Web Developement

• AutoCAD 3D Designs

• Network Administration

• Digital Marketing

E. WORK EXPERIENCE

Organization	Role

2022 Till Date CodeHub Technological Institute Co-Founder & Senior Developer

2020 Till Date Fiverr Freelancer Front End Developer

Sept. - Nov., 2020 Softrays Information Technology Front End Developement Instructor

Mar. - Apr., 2019 INEC Nigeria Registration Area Technical (RATECH) Officer During

General Elections, Osi LGA, Kwara State.

F. SKILL SET

Skill Proficiency Skill Proficiency

HTML & CSS	90%	AutoCAD	80%
React Js	93%	Network Administration	85%
Next Js	95%	Cisco Packet Tracer	79%
PHP	85%	MS Office	75%

G. PORTFOLIO

Visit http://taslim-eniolla.vercel.app to view portfolio.